[music]
>> Okay, now here is the build showcase.
So before we start, I just wanted to say
we are so close to 10k subs.
I'll be doing something special for that
for sure, so make sure to subscribe if
you like my content.
Also, my Discord server recently
transitioned into a PvE carry server.
So if you want to do NMDs and elders
>> [music]
>> carried for you, and then you get the
loot,
then you should come join up. Also, I
host it sometimes, so if you want to be
in videos like this, then
you know where to go.
Anyway, let's start with the damage
test. So I'll just build chains, and
then we'll see how much damage this
does. [music]
Okay, so with no buffs at all, we are
doing 1,010 damage at M1.
So that is actually pretty good.
And we'll see with our crits.
What is that? 3,000 or so?
Maybe 2,000.
And now
we can just eat
a glazed fish to get some melee damage
boosts.
We can also consume a gold, which gives
us some more.
And then also use order on our weapon.
And now this will bring our damage
all the way up to about 1,030,
1,040.
And our crits even more.
So that is some really good M1 damage.
But what you want to do with the build
is pretty simple. As usual, use your
towers, spam your critical.
And this will
get you to posture break, elder, and
maybe any boss
really quickly. Still four crates, it's
not changed.
And yeah, let's get on to the clips.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Mhm.